<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Responsi 1 Mobile H1D023076</string>
    <string name="club_history_text">
        <p>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Fulham Football Club, commonly known as Fulham FC or simply Fulham, is an English professional football club based in Fulham, London. Founded in 1879, the club holds the distinction of being London’s oldest professional football club, having originated as Fulham St. Andrew’s Church Sunday School FC and later joining the Southern League in the 1890s. Their home, Craven Cottage — situated on the banks of the River Thames — has been their base since 1896, creating a rich sense of history and continuity in West London.</p>
        <p>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Over the years, Fulham have experienced periods of both high achievement and struggle, embodying a true “yo-yo club” nature at times. After turning professional in December 1898, they climbed through the Southern League and joined the Football League in 1907. The club has seen various eras: in the mid-20th century stars like Johnny Haynes became club icons, and in 1975 they reached their only FA Cup final to date, though they were defeated by West Ham United. In recent decades they have navigated promotions and relegations between the top-tier Premier League and the Championship, finally establishing themselves again in the Premier League from the 2022-23 season onwards.</p>
        <p>&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Today, Fulham combine their storied past with modern ambition. They are known for their attractive playing style, development of youth talent through their academy, and a dedicated supporter base that treasures the riverside charm of Craven Cottage. Under current ownership and management, the club continues to build its infrastructure and competitiveness, aiming not only to survive in the Premier League but to challenge higher up the table. At the same time, they remain connected to their community roots in West London, epitomising the spirit of a historic club evolving in the modern era of English football.</p>
    </string>

</resources>